Welcome to the Dynamus and Curo AI
coding hackathon. This is your chance to
use Kuro, a very powerful coding agent
to build any project that you could
imagine and compete for your chance at
part of the $17,000
prize pool. I was actually talking to
the Curo team way back in July of last
year about doing this hackathon. Now,
finally, we are partnering up together
to bring this event to you, and I could
not be more excited. So, as an
introduction to the event right now, I
want to quickly show you what this
hackathon is all about, how you can make
a submission and compete. And then also,
there is a quick start guide that I want
to cover at a high level for you right
now. There is also a video that I have
for this landing page, which I'll link
to in the description. If you want to
watch the full guide where I actually go
through the entire quick start in
detail, definitely check this out right
here. So, right now, just a quick
introduction to get you in the know for
this really exciting event. And so this
hackathon has officially started January
5th. That's when this video is coming
out. And the submission period will go
until January 23rd. And then at that
point, we have the judging period,
figuring out who won the competition.
And then I'll be announcing the winners
on a live stream that I'm doing on
February 7th on my YouTube channel. And
all you have to do to register for this
hackathon, which you can do at any point
during the submission period, is just
click on the nice big join the hackathon
button right here. that will direct you
to create an account in the Dynamus
community. So, if you're not a member of
Dynamus already, it'll open up this Curo
Hackathon section for you. And then, if
you are a member of Dynamus already,
you'll just have this along with
everything else that we already have in
the community. So, this is a spot that
is open to the public because this
hackathon is open to everyone. This
community is where I'll be making all
announcements for the hackathon. And so
you'll see these in the primary
hackathon channel. And I'll be sure to
send all announcements to your email as
well. And once you're registered and
you're in the community here, also be
sure to read this pinned post. I have
the link here to make your submission
and then also everything that you need
to know at a high level is laid out
right here. I just want to make it as
easy as possible for you to participate,
have a good time, learn a lot, and
potentially win something big. And one
thing that I want to cover before I get
into what you can build for the
hackathon is getting your free credits
for the competition. I will be sending
out emails in waves throughout the first
week of the event, getting you your code
so you can claim your free credits. But
you don't have to wait for that to get
started because if you create a Curo
account right now, you get 500 bonus
credits that you can use within 30 days.
And so you can make a new account if you
want. If you already have a Curo
account, you probably already have these
credits applied. And so you don't have
to pay anything to get started. 500
credits will take you very far using
hero and then you can claim your other
credits very soon. And then going back
to our main page, I want to scroll down
and talk about what you can build for
the event. And it's actually pretty easy
to talk about this because literally the
only requirement is that you use Kira. I
mean, it makes sense, right? Cuz I'm
partnering with the Kuro team to bring
this event to you. They're the ones who
are sponsoring with the prize pool as
well. They're not sponsoring me
personally. Literally, they're only
sponsoring the prize pool. And so you
have to use Kira but other than that the
theme is completely open. You can build
any kind of application that your heart
desires that you can imagine. So you can
build web apps, AI agents, CLI tools,
APIs and microservices, automation
tools. You could build a mobile
application. It is entirely up to you.
There's probably a dozen other
categories I'm not even thinking about
here. But the world is your oyster. The
possibilities are endless. And so I've
got the documentation for either the
Kuro CLI or IDE linked right here if you
want to learn how to use these tools,
but also I have a quick start guide that
I'll talk about in a little bit that
makes it very easy for you to begin your
project to compete in the hackathon and
use Kirao. And so the CLI is preferred,
but you can use either in order to
compete in this hackathon and build your
application. And then so you know
exactly how your submission will be
judged, I also have the judging criteria
laid out here. So application quality,
how well you used Kirao, the CLI or IDE
if you want, how well you documented
your project, more on that in a little
bit, how unique or innovative your
solution is, and then also the
presentation because as a part of your
submission, we are asking for just a
simple 2 to 5 minute demo video. And
honestly, the biggest reason that I want
to require this as well is because I
want to see you excited about your
project as you show it to us. And then
the other thing as far as documentation
goes, there are some things that we want
you to include in your submission beyond
just the source code because we want to
see not just your finished project, but
your actual AI coding process as you are
working with Kira. So that includes your
steering documents. These are global
rules. That's what Kira calls global
rules. You have your prompts or
commands. These are the workflows that
you define in markdown. And then also
your devlog. And so the devlog is where
you can document your timeline,
decisions that you made, challenges that
you encountered and how you address
those. Basically just your entire
development journey of your solution. We
want you to document that and you can
really do it in any kind of format that
suits you best. And so altogether your
submission will have the source code,
documentation, a readme so that we can
get the project running ourselves and
then your demonstration video. And just
be sure to submit this by January 23rd
before midnight Pacific time. And now
the very last thing that I want to cover
with this page here before I go on to
the quick start is the rules. And I'll
keep it nice and simple here. And so the
main thing is this is not a team
competition. You have to have an
individual submission and you can only
make one submission. Now you can feel
free to work on many different projects
for the competition, but you have to
pick one in the end to submit to us. And
back in the community there, I have that
link for the submission form. It's going
to look like this. And so you just go
through this, fill out everything. Once
you have your project complete, you can
either upload as a zip file or link us
to a public GitHub repository. So,
entirely up to you how you share your
project. And then your video, your demo
video can be an unlisted YouTube video,
a Loom link, whatever you want to send
us for that. Now, the very last thing
that I want to cover for you is the
quick start. And I put a lot of time
into building this template for you to
make it as easy as possible to get over
that initial hurdle of starting your
project to compete. And so I linked to
this quite a few spots throughout the
homepage here. And so this is a GitHub
repository that you can use as a
template. You can just clone it locally.
And there are instructions here both to
get your project started for the
hackathon and how to use Curo at a high
level. And so the Curo guide markdown
right here. This is actually a fantastic
resource if you are familiar with other
AI coding assistants, but you want to
see what's different with Kuro and how
you use Kuro specifically. So I cover
what makes it different installation
instructions for different operating
systems. This is for the Kuro CLI. So I
focused on the CLI for the quick start,
but a lot of these things like how you
set up your Curo folder with your
steering documents and your prompts. All
of that will translate to the IDE as
well. So I cover all of those core
concepts, even some of the more advanced
things like tangent mode and knowledge
management between sessions, sub aents,
MCP servers. Kira is a very featurerich
AI coding assistant. And so if you go
through the read me here, it'll guide
you through everything from start all
the way to getting the first features
built for your project for the
hackathon. And so I have this quick
start command here that'll actually ask
you questions to walk you through
defining the steering documents that
will help guide your coding agent going
forward as you're building your project.
Then I also have a ton of workflow
commands built into the template that
you can use. And so this is an example
development workflow that you can go
through as you're building your project
with Kro. And so you can take a lot of
creative freedom here. You don't have to
follow the suggestions and commands that
I have for you here. But if you want to,
and there's also a lot of really solid
strategies I built into this, you can
definitely feel free to do so. And
again, I have a lot more information on
using the quick start in the video right
here. So, I'll link to this page and the
quick start in the description of this
video. And that, my friend, is
everything that I need to cover to
introduce you to the Dynamus and Curo
hackathon. I hope to see you compete in
the event. I'm really, really excited
for this. Thanks for watching and let me
know if you have any questions at all as
you get started with the